I'll see you later, Eren.
Mikasa, hey.
We should get back.
Um, where are we exactly?
Try asking me again when you're awake.
I'm up, I just, I don't know.
It's like the dream I was
having went on forever.
It's gone now.
What was it about?
[Gasp] Eren, have you been crying?
[Gasp]
See this, Halil?
Me and you are the only ones
who know where I've hidden it.
This is where we'll stash every
bit of money we get our hands on.
And once the sack is full,
we'll finally be able to afford
a nice place for everyone.
We would all like that.
But what if you get caught again?
You're going to end up
losing your left hand too.
Please don't make Grandpa cry again, Ramzi.
I know, but someone has to do it.
Right now, we've only got
those shabby little tents to live in.
They're not enough to keep out the cold.
More of us freeze to death each winter.
So listen, Halil.
If anything happens, make
sure everybody gets their share.
Don't say that.
[CIVILIAINS chatting and gasp]
[Gasps] Hide it!
What's going on?
The townspeople are running away?
But from what?
[Gasps]
[EREN] Later.
[EREN] I don't know how long after this.
[EREN] Every last one
of these people is killed.
The entire city is massacred.
No, I should say I massacre them.
It's already determined.
I imagine we learn that
our wish isn't possible.
We never find a way to save Paradis.
So everything here ends.
The homes, the animals, the
people, the lives they live, their dreams.
[Gasps]
If Mom were here, what would she think?
Would it be best if we
were the ones to die?
What if the King of the Walls
was right to choose death?
Even if our island was wiped out, the loss
of life would be nothing in comparison.
And if the Eldian people
disappeared, the Titans
and all the strife they
bring would be gone.
But an ending like that, I can't accept it.
[MAN A grunt]
I've seen this in my
memories of the future.
[MAN A grunt]
And it seems like I saved this boy.
[Boy groans]
Huh?
[MAN B and MAN C] Hm?
This refugee rat has been picking
people's pockets where we do our business.
Pest control may not be
too pleasant to look at, but it's
something we have to do
to hang on to our livelihoods.
It's not your problem, so
just keep walking. Or else...
Yeah, I guess it isn't.
What am I even thinking?
What difference does it
make if I help him now?
I know I kill him later.
[MAN A grunts]
Little theif!
I drowned this whole
world in a sea of blood.
How could I pretend to care about justice?
It seems the future won't change.
Thank you very much.
I'm the same as you, Reiner.
A half-assed piece of shit.
No, not the same. I'm worse.
Forgive me. I'm sorry.
So sorry.
[Gasp] For what? Why are you crying, sir?
Ramzi! Halil! Hurry!
They're almost here! Cabuk!
Run! Run!
Why aren't the Titans here?
The mountains!
No use! They're not slowing down!
The Titans are walking over the mountains!
Please, no!
Olecegiz.
There's nowhere else for us to escape to!
Did the Marleyans flee without warning us?
They move too fast!
Ramzi! Are we going to get tremble?
No, we're not! But we have to keep running!
I'm doing it for Eldia and the island.
But there's more than just that.
[REFUGEES scream]
[HAILI] The money.
[RAMZI] No, Haili!
The world I found outside the walls,
and the world I always
dreamed of, are nothing alike.
Halil!
[BOTH gasp]
It's so different from the
place I saw in Armin book.
When I learned that humanity
had survived out here,
I felt it.
I'd never been so let down.
[Scream]
I made a wish.
[Gasp]
That all of it would be wiped away.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hey! Open the gate! Please!
[REFUGEES scream]
[Banging]
Hello? Is anybody out there?
Anybody!
Dear.
Is this it?
Is the day of our judgement finally here?
[CIVILIANS screaming]
[GIRL CIVILAINS A screams]
[Car honking]
[CIVILIANS gasping]
[EVERYONE crying]
From the moment I was born,
those stifling walls were
the farthest I could see.
Water that glows like fire.
Fields of ice.
Sandy snowfields.
To witness all that
was to know the greatest
freedom this world could offer.
We're here!
We're free!
We found it.
Somewhere we can look
out and see everything.
Right, Armin?
Eren...
So your wounds are all better?
Annie?
Yeah. They've had enough time to heal.
Honestly, I'm amazed we got
the chance to catch our breath.
It's weird how at ease I feel.
Come, sit down, please.
I was hoping I would get
a chance to say thanks.
ARMIN gasps]
I really needed your
company those four years.
So thank you.
ARMIN gasps] Sure.
That loneliness was
enough to drive me crazy.
And you and Hitch offered
me something to hold on to.
Annie... But why did you do it?
You were talking to a rock the whole time.
Wasn't it frustrating that
I never answered you?
ARMIN gasps]
I mean, why not find a girl
who could hold a conversation?
Gasp]
That's not what I want.
What I wanted was to see you.
ANNIE gasps]
But why?
Uh... "Why?"
You have to get it by now, Annie.
You heard Hitch teasing me about it.
I don't.
[Ship horn blow]
Nothing makes sense.
What are we even doing out here?
Right now, hundreds of millions
of people are getting trampled,
and we're just floating along.
That's it.
You did it because you're good,
and good people are willing
to talk to their enemies.
You're trying to do the
same thing now, with Eren.
I could have broken out at any time.
You wanted to talk to the monster,
so you wouldn't have to fight it, right?
[ANNIE gasps]
Please don't leave yet.
Listen, I've said this before, but
"good" is just what people
call people who help them.
I can't count how many lives I've taken.
And not just soldiers in battle.
Civilians.
Even kids.
Now I've chosen to betray the
island where I was born and raised.
I've killed my own comrades.
If I'm "good," then that word is useless.
As a child, I made a promise to Eren
that one day we would all get to
explore this vast unknown world together.
I wanted to think I could keep it.
Learning what it was really like out
here must have been a painful lesson.
Yeah.
The world we'd spend our lives
dreaming of wasn't what we got.
But...
Even so,
a part of me still hope that there's
something more beyond the walls,
waiting to be found.
It's so quiet here.
It would appear the residents
of Odiha have already fled south.
All the ships set sail before we arrived.
Right. So then...
It comes down to your team.
Yes. The Azumabito clan will get
the flying boat airborne at any cost.
We've got to hurry! Get the cover!
Shit! The explosives are in the way!
Cut them off and toss them.
Wait. We might be able
to use these for something.
Load them up once the cover is off.
[FLACO scream] There's no way!
Commander Magath! My family!
Everyone back home in Liberio!
They can't all be gone!
By now, most of the Marleyan continent
has been flattened by the rumbling.
Then what are we doing? And why?
Who's left to save? Everybody is dead!
I'm sorry.
I wish I knew.
Annie.
You still don't have much
experience with the newer ODM gear.
This would be a good
time to test out your rig.
You can go practice with Reiner.
Get a feel for it.
Why would I?
Uh... If there's a chance we have
a duty to take it, it'll be tough.
But we still... Look, I told you on
the way over that I was done fighting.
So you're not going to be
joining us on the flying boat?
Sorry, but no.
This whole "saving humanity" idea...
I honestly just... don't understand it.
As Eldians and Marley, we
were caged and tortured from
birth by the "humanity"
you're so desperate to save.
That was the world I knew.
But the cage protected us, too.
And Eren trampled it flat.
If we stop the rumbling, we Eldians
will stand alone, against everyone.
I truly am sorry.
These people are giving all they have
for a chance to save their homelands.
And I feel for them.
But I'm done.
I don't have it in me to keep fighting.
If this is the end of it all.
I want to spend it... in peace.
[MIKASA gasps]
[ANNIE gasps]
[Gasps]
So when did this start?
When did what start?
Right. I get it.
Get what?
It's okay.
You don't need to suffer anymore.
[Gasps]
But you realize...
Armin will be coming
with us on the flying boat.
We're going to track down Eren.
I know that.
When you find him, what
do you expect to happen?
If saving the world means killing
Eren, will you have the will to do it?
I won't kill him.
Eren is strayed too far from home.
All I'm doing... is bringing him back.
Hey, before you go...
What happened to your old scarf?
I've still got it.
You're still hurt!
You need to get back in bed!
Thanks for your concern, but screw that.
I can sleep once I'm dead.
I've got a kid. You little shits
don't get to forget about me.
[ARMIN gasps]
[LEVI] Moving on.
Our bearded lady's
third elbow is healing up,
and it seems like she
survived her infection.
I'm going to make her
tell us where Eren is going.
If the Allied nations combine their
fleets to attack the island of Paradis...
They'll be assembling
here, at Karifa Naval Port.
After the raid on Liberio,
we'll allow a month for their
forces to gather before we
bring you in contact with Zeke.
With him, you'll be able
to use the power of the.
Founding Titan, and
activate a limited rumbling.
The outer wall around
Shiganshina holds several
hundred Titans, easily
enough to crush the whole fleet.
And there's nothing else
we need to worry about?
Will destroying their navies really
guarantee Paradis a few decades of peace?
Losing a fleet would be a death
blow to any nation's finances.
As long as we hid all the major powers,
nobody will have the means to hit us back.
But in the worst case,
this fortress in the.
Southern Mountains
could give us some trouble.
The airship research base there
may be a worthwhile secondary target.
If I had to guess, that's where
Eren will be heading next.
The air base at Fort Salta.
Makes sense.
He would want to get rid of any weapon that
could pose even the slightest
threat to the Founding Titan.
First he'll wipe out the United Fleet at
Karifa,
and then the airships at Fort Salta.
Didn't feel like getting
any more bones broken.
I want you all to do something for me.
Acknowledge the truth.
Zeke lost his battle, but he
was fighting for the right cause.
The Eldian Empire brought
2,000 years of misery to the
world, and the euthanization
plan was the way to fix it.
Surely you're able to see that by now.
Yeah, I can't deny it.
I thought I could show Eren a
better way, but I was powerless.
I couldn't give him
hope, or a path forward.
[Clattering]
[CONNY sighs]
All the fuel's unloaded!
Here's the last of it!
Good to hear! Go ahead and leave it there!
Please take the two of them with you.
Even if the kids stay on the ship,
they won't be out of harm's way.
But it's still safer than the flying boat.
Of course, I have no objection to that.
But do you believe they'll
be willing to accept it?
I can keep them in their cabin.
Just make sure they stay
there until we've gotten airborne.
And what about you?
I still have a debt to pay
to my fallen comrades.
I need to do my duty as a warrior.
Hange! We'll be ready for
takeoff sequence in about an hour!
Got it!
Well, you heard the man.
Everyone, give your ODM gear a final check.
[ALL] Roger that!
Two fingers are all I
need to get the job done.
I'm good to go.
Looks like I'm the only one running away.
It's fine, Annie.
This isn't your war.
You weren't in it for
Marley from the start.
You've already done more
than anyone could ask of you.
All this time, I've wanted to apologize.
To you and Bertholdt both.
When we lost Marcel, I forced the two
of you to go through with the mission.
If I'd just decided to turn back, then
all of us would have gotten to go home.
I'm the reason you never
saw your families again.
[Exhales] Even trying to say sorry
feels presumptuous.
Yeah, but I managed to talk
myself out of killing you. Barely.
[Gasp] Well done. I commend your restraint.
Look after Gabi and Falco.
Understood, sir.
Annie!
Take care of yourself, alright?
We'll see you around!
Hey, Armin.
You'd let her walk off like that?
Like what?
Now I'm worried.
This may not work without her.
It'll be hard, but she's been
through more than enough.
This is for the best.
I want Annie to just keep being Annie.
Are you two sure you want to join us?
If we do stop the rumbling, our lives
as Eldians won't be getting any easier.
We understand that.
But even so, we have a mission to finish.
General Magath's last order to
us was clear, and we'll carry it out.
It's time to work together
and do what must be done.
Pieck, I- I hope someday you'll
let me
feel Cart Titan's body heat under
me as we ride over the...
Quit that. Of all the times to be creepy.
You know the Titans are never going to
love you back, three eyes. Quit pushing it.
I think I'll win her over yet.
Levi, do you think they're
all watching over us?
The comrades we've lost...
Do you think they'd be proud
of what we're doing here?
That's enough of that talk.
You're sounding just like him.
Good. Begin fueling and keep up the pace!
Roger that, sir!
We made it. We outran the rumbling.
This could still work.
[Gasps]
Flock!
Don't tell me... Did he let the
ship drag him all the way here?
Hange!
He shot up the tank! We can't fill it!
[ALL gasps]
We're trapped! The boat is grounded!
Don't give up!
It'll fly if we can get these holes sealed.
[Gasp] Grab the welding tools!
How long's it gonna take?
Patching it with tin will be the
fastest way. An hour should be just...
We haven't got an hour.
No, no, no!
It's here.
The rumbling is here.
Don't...
Please...
Don't... do it...
[HIZURU ENVOY C] Check the engine.
We're here, Flock.
Everyone on the island...
They'll all be killed.
Our...
Devil... Is the only one...
Who can save us.
Our only... hope.
No! Hold on!
He's gone.
[JEAN gasp]
It's true, Flock.
We can't protect them all.
But still...
We have no choice but to try.
And even if we fail today...
Maybe someday...
Stop! Why are you doing this?
The Titans are right on top of us.
[GABI] Let us out Annie!
[ANNIE] That enough!
Armin? Do you have any ideas?
Yeah.
Only one, though.
I can stay here, buy you some time.
No, that won't work.
We're gonna need you against Eren.
You're our fallback.
Go. I can cover the rear.
You think that's any better?
If we're going to stand a chance, we
can't use any of our Titan power yet.
We wouldn't be facing this
situation if it weren't for me.
I dragged you all here over
the bodies of your comrades.
It's time I made it right.
Commander...
Armin Arlert.
As of now, I appoint you 15th
Commander of the Scout Regiment.
[ARMIN gasp]
There's one quality this
post requires above all else.
An uncompromising desire
to understand our world.
No one embodies that more than you.
They're in your hands now.
Short retirement speech, I know.
Alright, bye guys.
Oh yeah, this also means
Levi's your subordinate.
Better work him to the bone.
[ARMIN gasps]
Hey, that's your goodbye?
I know you get it, Levi.
I've been waiting so long for this.
My time has come.
So please, I want to ride the high to
the end and make a really awesome exit.
Let it happen, okay?
[HANGE gasp]
Dedicate your heart.
[HANGE laugh]
I didn't think I'd ever hear you say that.
Hange.
[HANGE gasp]
Wow. Titans truly are the
most marvelous creatures.
[HANGE yells]
The tank is sealed!
Start fueling now! Hurry! Let's move!
[HIZURU ENVOY A]
They're, here, its now or never!
Start fueling, we're out of time!
Get the engines turning!
Push it onto the ramp!
[Grunts]
More time!
Shit!
Launch the ship.
Come on.
[Yells]
Hange, no!
See you around, Hange.
Just watch us.
[Gasps]
Where's the flying boat?
On its way.
[HANGE gasp]
They made it.
You did exactly what you needed to, Hange.
Erwin?
Everyone.
[HANGE gasp]
I see.
[Chuckle] Gotta say, being commander of the
scouts is a ridiculous amount of stress.
That Eren kid's a handful.
It's tough.
There's time now.
We can talk about it.
Thanks.
We're half empty.
Yeah.
Ran out of time before they could fill it.
Do we have enough fuel to reach Fort Salta?
I'll find a way to make it happen.
Hange died to get this thing flying,
with humanity's last hope on board.
So we're gonna get to
that base, whatever it takes.
I swear it.
In return, you all have
to stop the rumbling.
Please promise me that.
Yeah. We will.
Thank you.
Okay.
Let's lay out the plan.
Based on what you saw, does the Founding
Titan's body look something like this?
Yeah.
Though what I saw wasn't really that much.
It's an ugly pile of bones crawling
along on its belly, like some gigantic bug.
If it works like most Titans, Eren is
controlling it from the nape of its neck.
But the Warhammer's power is in play here.
That changes the game.
Exactly.
We don't know which
part of the body he's in.
But we don't need to land a precise hit.
We've got a weapon that can annihilate it.
The same weapon that laid waste
to the port at Liberio in an instant.
We can drop the Colossal Titan on him.
We could. It's a guaranteed
way to destroy the Founder.
[MIKASA gasps]
But before that, I still
want to try to talk things out.
If we can't convince Eren to stop the
Rumbling himself, I'll be our last resort.
Coming up with the last
resort first isn't a bad idea.
But Zeke holds the Founder's power.
Eren controlling it through him.
We don't need to blow his whole body away.
Killing Zeke should end the Rumbling.
You're right. It might work.
No way to be sure, but
that was Hange's theory.
Still doesn't help unless
we figure out where Zeke is.
Easy enough problem to solve.
We dig into that
bone heap and force
the hairy bastard out.
[Sighs]
We'll find him. And I'll cut him down.
With your help. Are we agreed?
Got it, Captain. I'm with you.
We had to kill so many of our friends
just to get this thing into the sky.
If we back down, we'll have
butchered our own people in vain.
All of this is to stop the Rumbling.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Me too.
Reiner, I had to shoot
Samuel and Daz at the port.
I carved up people I've
known since we were cadets.
They died cursing my
name, calling me a traitor,
while I told myself I
was saving the world.
Was it the same for your team?
You, Bertholdt,
and Annie. Is this what it felt like?
Yeah. I know my sins are beyond redemption.
I doubt I'll ever forgive myself, even
if we save what's left of humanity.
Still, we've gotta try.
Even knowing it'll never be enough.
I needed to hear that.
Thank you. It won't make up for
all we've done.
But still, we gotta do what we can.
Reiner, I shouldn't have judged you.
I'm sorry.
[REINER gasps]
[JEAN] I became a murderer to
protect the lives of other people,
just like you. I can't pretend
your sins are greater than my own.
You know, Eren told me something
similar just before the Liberio raid.
Right now, I feel like I might have
some idea what's going on in his mind.
Do you think he might be
hoping we can beat him?
[ALL gasp]
What do you mean by that?
Not sure.
It's a feeling I can't really explain.
Actually, there's one
thing I still don't get.
Eren has the power of the Founder.
He can control all Eldians and all Titans.
He should be able to keep us from
using our Titan powers. But he hasn't.
Are you trying to say that Eren has
been giving us free reign this whole time?
That's right. He's letting us do all this.
It's like he wants to find out how we're
going to respond to what he's done.
Why would he? He's gotta know
there's a chance we'll stop the rumbling.
That's just it. If I were in his place,
if all that blood was on my
hands, I couldn't bear it.
I think I'd want somebody to
take the Founder's power from me.
If nobody could, then I'd want somebody
to end it.
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
We're back here?
Oh yeah.
[REINER gasp]
[PIECK gasp]
The hell? Was he eavesdropping on us?
Eren! Listen to me!
We've won, okay? It's over!
Paradis is safe now!
The world has seen
the terror of the rumbling!
If anyone ever attacks the island
again, it won't be for centuries!
We'll be able to negotiate a non-aggression
treaty with the other countries!
You never need to kill anyone again, Eren!
We can go home and live our lives in peace!
We understand that we screwed up!
We were wrong to
push you this far, but you
don't have to keep going!
Eren...
Eren! We'll figure out a way
to handle things from here!
Please, stop this bloodbath and let us try
to make the best of
what's left of the world!
Yeah, that's right.
Eren!
I hated you for what happened to Sasha!
But I know you were
hurting as much as any of us!
I could have seen it back then
if I'd put myself in your shoes!
Eren... I want to help you
carry the burden of your sins.
We all do.
Because there are sins as well.
We're here. Don't push us away!
Please, Eren! Quit running! Let's go home!
You heard your friends, Eren.
If they insist, I'll
let you off with just
one good kick in the ass.
Speak up! You gonna let
us do all the talking or what?
Eren!
[EREN] The rumbling will not stop.
And the future of the island of Paradis
will not be left to the whims of fate.
I will keep moving forward.
[ALL gasp]
Over there.
[MIKASA panting]
Eren!
Wait? What the hell? That's a kid!
You're right. But that kid is Eren!
Eren!
Why won't you listen to us?
Do you not trust us to handle this?
Wait, Eren! Why are you still
letting us use the Titan powers?
We can talk as long as we like here!
So talk to us!
We've been together our whole lives!
We're here for you now,
so stop running away! Eren!
I will hold freedom in my
hands by taking it from this world.
But from you, I will take nothing.
You are all free to
oppose me and defend the
world's freedom, just as I
am free to move forward.
Our convictions can never be
reconciled, and our wills will not bend.
There is only one way for
this to be resolved. Fight!
But then.
Then why do this? If talking
won't help, then why bring us here?
I brought you here to say
that there is nothing to say.
You will only stop my advance when you stop
me from breathing, and you are free to try.
[Thudding]
[Gasps]
What happened? You okay?
Well, it looks like I had it right.
Then there's really no other way?
Guess it's safe to say we're done
negotiating. So, Commander, what's next?
Where is this ship headed?
We'll be on course for Hizuru
these next several days.
I have faith that Lady Mikasa and her
comrades will be able to stop the rumbling.
However, I fear we'll learn my country
is nonetheless in a state of collapse.
Gonna be hard to find anything
to eat but fish for a while, huh?
I'm sure you'll find the
seafood in Hizuru is exquisite.
Glad to hear it. Oh, I forgot about birds.
It was thanks to me that
Zeke and Eren were united.
I could put every waking
moment toward atoning for
my part in the slaughter
and still die unredeemed.
So, if you could make that
choice again, what would you do?
Leave the Eldians to their own
devices and watch Paradis die?
It's useless to speak of
turning back the clock.
Yet my regret will surely weigh
on me for as long as I live.
I can't rightly call myself a
friend to the Eldian people
when I never truly acted in
the interest of their survival.
Instead, I forged an
alliance of convenience for
the financial and social
betterment of the Azumabito.
I wonder why we so often fail
to see what matters till it's lost.
Why we can't recognize the value in one
another beyond what benefits ourselves.
You're right. We learn too late.
Annie, I... I had a dream.
Did you? From Galliard?
No, it was from Zeke.
And it... was a memory.
They told us back in training that
the female Titan can manifest the
abilities of the rest of the Nine by
taking in parts of their bodies, right?
Yeah. The female is best
suited for that trick.
You wouldn't believe the stuff they fed me.
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNIE] What of it?
Just like we thought!
Then there might still
be something we can do!
But how can we be sure it'll work?
Will you two shut up?
Go carry some coal or something!
Did you say you had a vision
of one of Zeke's memories?
That's right. I think it's because I became
a Titan by drinking his spinal fluid.
And now Falco started manifesting
aspects of the Beast Titan!
Okay. Keep talking.
In the memory I see most clearly,
I'm flying. Up above the clouds.
And as I look down, somehow
it feels like I could do that too.
[ANNIE gasp]
That's Fort Salta on the Mesa, right?
Are there really airships there?
Couldn't say. But you bet everything
on a long-shot plan to steal one.
I guess we won't find
out if your gamble paid off
until we get to the end of the line.
Will we, Eldian?
Careful how you talk to me, Marleyan.
That gamble is the only reason
you're not a stain in a foot-shaped crater.
If it doesn't pay off, your family
dies in the rumbling with the rest of us.
If you betray us, you die
here of a gunshot wound.
But if the plan works,
you all see another day.
I don't give a damn if
the odds are against us.
We're all gonna come
out of this thing alive.
It'll be okay, Mrs. Brown.
They're a tough couple
of kids, and they've
got Reina and Colt
there to look after them.
Right now they're trapped on that
island with the devils themselves!
How can they possibly survive out there?
[BOTH sob]
If she'd never become a warrior, we could
have at least been together in the end.
Reiner.
Hey, Mr. Finger. Might as well
toss that thing out the window.
My girl gave up everything
to earn this armband.
Sacrificed her whole life
to save her dying father.
Come on...
Hey, up there!
[Gasp]
Oh no, they've taken off!
Full speed ahead!
Even just one will be enough!
Yeah, yeah, I know!
Watch that. That cloud. In the distance.
The rumbling... It's here.
It caught up to us.
[ALL chattering]
They're gone! Every last one is gone!
No, after we've made it this far... Why?
This is the end.
[Gasps]
Hold on. They're not evacuating. The
airships are heading towards the Titans!
And what does that mean?
It's a bombing run!
They're attacking the Titans from
the sky where they can't hit back!
Betting the future of
humankind on one huge air raid!
It's an air raid?
Then maybe there's still hope.
Attention! All airship units and
soldiers stationed at Fort Salter.
This is where we make our final stand.
The last bastion of mankind.
The immeasurable weight of
this moment now falls upon you.
But in victory or in defeat, the
burden is not rightfully yours to bear.
That responsibility lies with
those of us who came before you.
We cultivated hate.
Nurtured our resentments.
We let ourselves
believe that could save us.
And what came of our failings, we
simply dumped onto the "island of devils."
This is the result.
Those failings gave rise
to the monster you see.
And it's marching our hatred back upon us.
So if, somehow, we can
secure a future for our world,
I vow to never repeat those same mistakes.
So help me, God.
Miss Barina!
Leonhart] Karina.
All these years, when I looked at my
little boy, I just saw a tool for revenge.
So how could I call myself a mother?
We're the same.
I hope you will make that vow with me.
To break away from this era of mutual hate.
Continuing approach.
Airships are in formation.
Preparing for bombardment.
Descending to altitude.
To build a new world of
mutual care and understanding.
And let today be our last
goodbye to our own monsters.
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER B gasps]
The attack Titan is making a move!
Commence bombardment!
Bombs away!
They're too high!
The bombs aren't landing on targets!
This is our only chance.
All units release payloads immediately!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER B gasps]
[MARLEYAN SOLIDER A]
All airship units have been lost.
No survivors.
Forgive us, children.
[MULLER] We've failed you again.
Mommy, they're coming.
The Titan started slowing down.
I'm scared.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sure that Annie and
Reiner are still alive on Paradis.
Yes.
[ELDIAN DAUGHTER b gasps]
What's that?
In the clouds.
Damn it! They're nearly dry!
Target sighted! Prepare to jump!
What about you? Hurry up and get over here!
I'm staying! We're going to
drop you straight onto the target!
Let me worry about
getting this thing back down.
Don't jump till you're damn
sure you'll land on the founder!
Onyankopon!
[ALL gasps]
Furry shit bag. The Beast is in the field!
Good! Then we don't have to look for it!
You know the plan!
The Beast Titan is priority one!
Destroying him could
end this battle in one shot!
It's time to stop the rumbling!
[ONYANKOPON grunts]
[ONYANKOPON] Now!
[ARMIN] Eren!
[Grunt]
Shit! I can't touch down!
[REINER yells]
[JEAN] Hang on, Reiner!
[Grunt]
[BOTH gasp]
That's the Armored Titan,
and the Cart Titan's there too!
All those soldiers are wearing ODM gear.
It's them.
The forces of Paradis are
trying to end the rumbling!
Reiner.
Eren.
You said there was nothing
to say, but you were wrong.
I've got a question,
and you will answer it.
What do you really mean
when you say you're free?
Ending Song
www.tvsubtitles.net