[ELDIAN DAUGHTER B]
What's that?
In the clouds.
Target sighted! Prepare to jump!
What about you?
Hurry up and get over here!
I'm staying.
We're gonna drop you
straight onto the target!
Let me worry about getting
this thing back down.
Don't jump till you're damn sure
you'll land on the Founder!
Onyankopon!
Furry shitbag.
The Beast is in the field!
Good, then we don't
have to look for him!
You know the plan.
The Beast Titan is priority one!
Destroying him could end
this battle in one shot!
It's time to stop the rumbling!
Now!
[Grunts]
Eren!
[CONNY]
Shit. I can't touch down!
[Yells]
Hang on, Reiner!
[Grunting]
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER A]
That's the Armored Titan,
and the Cart Titan's there, too!
All those soldiers are wearing
ODM gear. It's them.
The forces of Paradis are
trying to end the rumbling!
[KARINA]
Reiner!
[ARMIN]
Eren.
You said there was nothing
to say, but you were wrong.
I've got a question
and you will answer it.
What do you really mean
when you say you're free?
Looks like that was
just an empty husk.
Killing it accomplished nothing.
[ARMIN]
As I feared.
The War Hammer's
abilities are being used
to hide the real Zeke
somewhere in the Founding Titan.
What, you're telling us
that we have to root out
one tiny human body from
this giant mess of bones?
There's no way.
It can't be done!
I'm sorry, Armin, but it's time
to face the facts! You have--
Yeah, I know!
[BOTH gasp]
Exactly one minute from now,
I'll blast these bones apart.
Use the Cart to get clear!
[MIKASA]
Armin.
Eren's aware that this
attack might be coming,
so I can't imagine
this'll kill him!
But still, if I do enough
damage to the Founding Titan,
we might be able to find
Zeke and Eren's bodies!
Be careful, Armin!
[JEAN] If you get into trouble,
don't worry about us.
Just transform on the spot!
[ARMIN] Those who can't
sacrifice anything
can't change anything.
I know that.
If I can't let it go,
its not worth holding on to.
No more clinging to
false hope for comfort.
I have to deal with Eren.
Armin!
[Gasps]
[All gasps]
[ELDIAN A]
Three, two, and pull!
[YOUNG ELDIAN A]
He's not moving.
[DOCTOR A]
But he is breathing.
He took a bad hit to the head.
Do you think he
brought those soldiers from Pardis?
Uh! Hey! Can you hear me?
Annie Leonhart! Do you know her?
She's my daughter!
I need to find her!
Please, sir. Answer me!
Reiner! They're coming!
[Yells]
What the hell are these things?
[JEAN] Judging from their
looks and how they act,
they don't seem
like Pure Titans.
What now? We're gonna run
out of Thunder Spears soon.
More importantly, we need
to find out if Armin's okay!
If he'd received so
much as a papercut,
he'd've transformed on the spot.
Which means he's being
restrained, but he's not hurt.
The problem is that he was
whisked off towards Eren's ass
and there are countless
Titans blocking our path.
Even if I were in perfect shape,
charging into that
wouldn't be my Plan A.
So stay calm, and let's think.
Mikasa, listen to me.
Before you rush in there,
let me try and draw
the bulk of them away.
That isn't going
to work, Captain.
I've figured out what
we're dealing with.
These husks...
[PIECK TITAN]
...are all the people
who bore the Power
of the Nine before us.
I don't know if their minds
are still in there or not.
But I'm betting the Founding
Titan has the ability
to resurrect them as many
times as it needs to.
This army of battle-tested
Titans was built for one reason:
to fight.
There's no way.
We can't beat that.
[PIECK TITAN]
Agreed.
Which means we can't afford
to be so easy going with this.
And, well, I'm not even
friends with Eren.
Huh?
Hey, what are you--?
Pieck, wait!
Damn it to hell.
No matter how you look at it,
the head's the place
to hit first!
This has been my
goal from the start!
No! Wait!
This nightmare ends right now!
[REINER]
Pieck!
Galliard?
[JEAN]
I'm with you, Reiner!
Do your best to pin
him down for me!
[Gasps]
You good, Captain?
[LEVI growls]
Focus. We need to
save Armin, and fast.
That's our only path
through this mess.
Without him, all of us
will die here for nothing.
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER A]
A force from Paradis
has engaged the Attack Titan,
but the trajectory of the
rumbling hasn't changed!
If this keeps up we'll
still be trampled!
Well, we can't just sit
back and do nothing.
All troops, meet the
enemy with cannonfire.
--[MARLEYAN SOLDIER B] Sir!
--Uh. Pardon, sir.
But the vast majority
of our personnel
were deployed ealier
on the airships.
With the troops we have left,
we'll struggle to man
even three cannons.
That may be so,
but its no reason
for us to sit back
and do nothing.
As we speak, a few brave people
are fighting desperately
on that monstrosity's back.
Just what do you think
they're fighting for?
Reiner! Incoming!
[LEVI yells]
[LEVI]
Hurry!
Mikasa!
[ARMIN]
I was naive.
My mind's fading.
After everything
we've been through,
you're just gonna
suffocate me...
...Eren?
No, this isn't him. It's her.
Eren said he'd move forward
while leaving all of us
free to oppose him,
so this resistance is
coming from the Founder.
It's the will of Ymir.
She's not under his control
any more than we are.
She wants this
genocide to happen.
And the Founder is invincible.
Against her, there's
nothing I can do.
So what? Is that it, then?
Is this where it all ends?
[REINER TITAN roaring]
[REINER gasps]
[REINER]
Bertholdt.
[REINER TITAN yelling]
[BOTH]
Reiner!
[JEAN]
Damn it. Are you kidding?
Stay with us, Conny!
Hey, Captain!
I'm sorry. My ODM gear's shot.
Not sure what to do.
Me neither.
My right trigger got
busted somehow,
so I can't pull us up.
Jean! Just let me go!
I can still transform
one more time!
Yeah, and then what?
You'll just be trampled
by the rumbling,
even with your armor.
I gotta say, Reiner,
for a Titan with that name,
it sure does break a lot.
[REINER]
Do you still think we can win?
[JEAN]
Nope. But I don't care.
I wanna fight to the bitter end.
We're Scouts, Reiner.
Not knowing when to give up
is what makes us who we are.
[Gasps]
Okay.
No!
[LEVI yells]
[MIKASA yells]
[Gasps]
[CONNY]
Captain!
[MIKASA]
Bring it on!
I'm stronger than
any of you, got it?!
So you'd better come
at me at once,
'cause no matter how--
[ANNIE]
You're kinda in the way, Mikasa!
Grab on!
I know.
Honestly, I never imagined
that a Titan would be
able to fly, either.
But he pulled it off,
so here I am.
Didn't have much choice.
That said, I'm glad to be here.
[ELDIAN C] A bird.
It's got people on its back!
[ELDIANS chattering]
[REINER] And you, Gabi?
Why are you here?
[GABI] Because I can fight!
Isn't that obvious?
You guys never should've
left us behind!
Annie!
Look, the Azumabito's
ship ended up sinking.
[Gasps]
[ANNIE] It couldn't withstand
Falco's Titan transformation.
Even though we had no
proof he could fly,
Kiyomi agreed to let
him make an attempt.
She put her faith in us,
and now we need to live up to it
by doing what it takes
to stop the rumbling!
Gabi.
Hang on, where's Arm--
I mean, where's Pieck?
[MIKASA] Armin was captured.
His life's in danger.
[Gasps]
[MIKASA] The Titan that took him
should be back by the tailbone.
Annie, we need your help.
Your childhood friends
sure do have a way
of getting themselves captured.
But yeah, I'll help
you get him back.
[GABI]
What about Pieck?
[REINER]
She's by the skull.
She tried to blast the nape,
but the War Hammer
Titan caught her.
[GABI]
To blast it?
[LEVI] We're gonna need
to split up. Agh.
Captain!
One group will go to
the tail and save Armin.
We're gonna need the
Colossal Titan's explosion.
The other group will move
towards Eren's head
and try to blow up his neck.
We'll form two teams and
launch a two-pronged assault.
We no longer have the luxury
of worrying about Eren.
Hell, we never had
it to begin with.
[MIKASA]
But, Captain--
[CONNY]
But what?
If Falco hadn't miraculously
flown in and saved us,
we'd already be dead!
That's right.
And we wouldn't have
accomplished a single thing.
You, too?
Damn it.
I had a long list of things to
tell that dumbass off about.
Shit.
Look, I don't wanna
give up on Eren, either!
But hell, thanks
to my screw-up,
the captain can barely
fight at this point.
And even if he were fine,
we're up against
the Founding Titan!
How can we win if we hold back?
Mikasa. I'm sorry.
But our only choice
is to kill Eren.
[Gasps]
[ANNIE]
Mikasa. Mikasa.
Mikasa!
You can just concentrate
on rescuing Armin, okay?
[Gasps]
Leave the rest to them. You
don't have to think about it.
[MARLEYAN SOLDIERS gasp]
It looks like they're
about to make
another run at the Attack Titan!
We can't give up either!
Even if it's just
a couple cannons,
it's better than nothing!
Are those refugees?
[MARLEYAN OFFICER A]
No. Look close.
Their sleeves are faded where
the armbands used to be.
You're Eldians, right?
Wait. Let's keep our heads.
We've got wounded.
We only came to seek aid.
Yeah, well, we don't
have time to give it!
Now tell us why
you're really here!
It's like I told you,
Mr. Leonhart.
Marleyans will never
help us willingly.
[ELDIAN F] Good thing
we outnumber them, then.
Probably have more
combat experience, too.
[YOUNG ELDIAN MAN A]
Bet you're right.
We're the ones they sent to die
on the front lines after all.
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER B]
Drop your guns, Eldians!
[ANNIE'S DAD]
Stop!
[CONDUCTOR A] Drop your
guns like you were told!
[ANNIE'S DAD] You?
Conductor, since when did--?
[Footsteps]
[MARLEYAN ARTILLERYMAN A]
Secretary Müller!
[ANNIE'S DAD gasps]
[Gunshots]
Gunshots?
People are still trying
to kill each other?
Falco! Look out for projectiles!
[Gasps]
[REINER]
Incoming!
[Yells]
Jean! Reiner!
You'd better not get killed!
Right. Same goes for you guys.
Now, to get the Warhammer
Titan's attention.
[REINER] Pieck, please find
a way to hold out.
[REINER TITAN yells]
Now, Jean! Move it!
I won't be long.
Just hang on...
...till I can reach
that detonator!
[JEAN]
Agh! That's just our luck.
Of course there'd be
even more of them!
[PIECK screams]
Could go for some ODM
gear myself right now!
I can't get close
enough. Damn it!
Pieck! You need to run for it!
Jean, if you think that
the Cart is just a utility Titan
that's not cut out for combat,
you're dead wrong!
[PIECK]
With the Cart's endurance,
as long as I'm not
taken out myself,
I can transform
hundreds of times!
[PIECK]
As many as it takes!
So leave me be.
You just focus on getting
to that detonator!
Though hundreds of victories
won't do me much good
against millions of enemies.
[ANNIE] They're even using
Bertholdt as a puppet.
How could they?
There it is!
That one, the pig thing!
Or whatever it is.
[ANNIE]
Which one?
Right there!
The weird one! See it?
[ANNIE] Where? Which one
of the Nine Titans is it?
[MIKASA]
Might be a Cart, or a Beast!
Or maybe a Jaw?
[ANNIE]
That's not helpful!
Give me a serious
description, will you?
I did!
There! The Titan that
just started running away!
[ANNIE]
That one? Isn't that an Okapi?
[MIKASA]
What the hell's an Okapi?
[ANNIE]
Go, Falco!
We'll corner that Okapi
thing at the tailbone
and get Armin back!
Good luck, guys.
I'll support you from
here with this gun!
I doubt that thing'll do much
against Titans like these.
[LEVI] Need to find Zeke.
Where could he be?
[LEVI] Even if I do find him,
I'm dead weight right now.
Dammit!
[LEVI]
I followed him for years
without ever botching
one of his orders.
Except this last one.
Why's it given me so much grief?
[LEVI] Could be that we
already served our purpose
a long time ago.
Maybe our mission ended
on the day those brats
set foot in the sea.
[LEVI] But is this what you
dedicated your hearts for?
Did you die so that others
could be trampled?
[LEVI]
No.
The dream you painted
of a world without Titans
was absurdly idealistic--
a place of pure joy.
It had to be... for it to
be worth what you gave.
Erwin, I-I didn't choose you
and I don't regret that.
[LEVI] I'm entrusting
the future to someone
with the same look in
his eyes as all of you.
Conny! It went your way!
Get back here!
[ANNIE] No! It's running
back to the skull!
[MIKASA]
Annie!
[Yells]
[MIKASA]
Stop running, you damn okapi!
[Gasps]
[ANNIE TITAN yells]
[MIKASA]
Annie!
We all need to stick together
or we'll be too easy to kill!
[MIKASA] The okapi's headed
towards Bertholdt!
Not good.
Behind us!
[ARMIN] You're my body and
I'm telling you to move,
so why won't you do it?
You have to move,
I'm begging you!
If you don't,
they'll all be killed!
Reiner. Pieck. Jean.
Conny. Mikasa. Annie.
Every last one of
them is gonna die!
Get up, you waste of space!
Human garbage!
Worthless piece of shit!
[ARMIN]
I hate you. I hate you.
And I always have!
Because you've never done
anything but betray me!
The hopes pinned on us...
The responsibilities
we accepted...
The second life we were given...
You haven't done a thing
with any of it!
So get up.
How dare you lie
here dead! Get up!
Get your worthless
ass off the ground!
[Screams]
[REFUGEES screaming]
[BABY A crying]
[Inaudible]
[ARMIN]
Sand.
Wait, think.
If I had already suffocated,
if I was already dead,
I wouldn't be able to think.
This isn't a dream, or a hallucination,
or the afterlife.
This place is real.
It's the world of the Paths.
I should be inside
a Titan's mouth right now,
so how do I know what's
happening to my friends?
Is it because, as Eldians,
all of us are connected
through the Paths?
If that's true, there might be
something I can accomplish here.
That's right. I need to think.
I need to think!
Hello, Zeke.
Come take a seat,
old friend of Eren's.
I'm guessing you were
consumed by Ymir, too?
[ZEKE]
For a long, long time,
the universe was
a chaotic mess...
of light and matter.
[ZEKE] From that mess,
countless insignificant things
came into and out of being.
Till eventually
something survived.
Something now known as "life."
Life survived for one reason:
It had the ability to multiply,
to spread itself far and wide.
In order to multiply, life had
to continuously change its form
to adapt to different
environments.
It's why we are as we are now.
Constantly spawning, and
expanding, and grasping at more.
The sole objective of
life is to multiply.
Sand. Pepples. Water.
They don't seek to multiply.
Yet life will never stop
struggling to do so.
Extinction runs counter
to the goal of multiplying,
so to make us run from death,
life cursed us with fear.
Like anyone, she did what she
could to escape the suffering
that fear brings.
She created a stronger, larger,
seemingly immortal body,
and then she escaped
into a world
where death doesn't even exist.
That's the truth
of the Founder Ymir,
and this is the world
she escaped to.
If that's the case, then
what's Ymir's objective now?
What drives her?
A good question.
I've spent a maddening
amount of time
trying to understand
the Founder.
She possessed power that
most have never dreamed of.
Yet she still couldn't
defy King Fritz.
What made her stay here
for 2,000 years
obeying that long dead man?
Clearly, there was something
she couldn't let go of.
Eren managed to figure out
what it was, while I failed.
And so, Ymir sided with him.
I need you to tell me.
How might someone return to
the outside world from here?
Who can say?
Don't really think
it's possible, myself.
Please, Zeke. I'm far
from ready to give up.
And why is that?
Uh, well, because I--
You still seek to multiply? Why?
Is continuing the species
really that important to you?
One might say that all this
is just the tragic result
of life's being ruled by fear.
We face a calamity of fear,
fed by the pointless
mechanics of life.
My comrades are still
fighting out there!
And we still have time
to save countless people
from a terrifying end!
People are fighting
fear as we speak!
But would it be
so awful to lose?
We'll all face death in time.
Why fight so hard to delay it?
As death comes,
I suspect that we might find
ourselves feeling relief.
No longer manipulated
by the body's urges,
or driven to multiply
without knowing
if any of this has a point.
We may feel like
we've been set free.
[ARMIN gasps]
[ARMIN]
The sun was starting to set.
And I was racing
Eren and Mikasa,
racing to the tree on the hill.
Eren started running right
after suggesting the race.
Mikasa deliberately
lagged behind him.
And I was last, of course.
But the wind was
slightly warm that day,
and it felt good
just to be running.
As the wind stirred
the dead leaves,
this strange, lovely thought
popped into my head.
I felt like maybe I'd been born
to race Mikasa and
Eren up that hill.
On rainy days, I would feel
the same way as I sat and read.
I felt it one time as I was
feeding acorns to a squirrel.
Even just strolling through
the market with my friends,
I had this feeling
that those insignificant moments
were incredibly precious.
Where'd you get that?
Huh? I just found it
buried in the sand.
But why would it be here?
Can't say.
But even though this
isn't useful to me,
even though I'm sure it'll
never help me to multiply,
to me, it's a truly
precious thing.
[Gasps]
[ZEKE]
That's right.
We would just throw the ball,
catch it, and throw it again.
Over and over.
There was no meaning behind it.
And yet it was just as you said.
I would've been happy to go
on playing catch forever.
[BOTH gasp]
Uh! Pieck!
I can rejoin the fight
once my arm is healed!
They'll kill us first.
Let's fall back and
regroup with Reiner!
[PIECK gasps]
Reiner!
[REINER]
Jean! Pieck!
Annie, no!
What the hell?
[PIECK]
Porco! Marcel!
[Gasps]
[REINER]
Ymir!
[CONNY] D-Did Bertholdt
just save all our lives?
I don't understand.
But still, I won't let this
chance slip away!
I made the shot!
You've got my friend.
Give him back!
Armin!
[Yells]
Annie!
[ARMIN coughing]
[ARMIN]
Annie.
Hey, Armin.
Thanks, guys. And I'm sorry.
But now,
I'm ready to fight.
[CONNY]
Annie, behind you!
[BOTH gasp]
[GABI]
What's going on?
Some of those Titans
just switched sides!
It sure looks that way.
[ZEKE]
Hey! Levi!
[Gasps]
[ZEKE]
Over here!
It can't be.
Missed me something awful,
eh, Levi? I know!
I can't say that I've felt the
same about you though!
Zeke.
What's happening
with these Titans?
It's actually all
thanks to Zeke.
[MIKASA]
What did he do?
[ARMIN] He awakened our comrades
in the world of the Paths
where life and death
have no meaning.
All Eldians are connected
by way of the Paths.
That's probably because
the Founder Ymir
is seeking connection.
I think she wants
something from us.
[ARMIN]
Bertholdt.
Mr. Ksaver, I failed to
turn our dream into reality.
And I still know we were right.
The euthanization plan would've
saved countless lives.
That said...
If it meant I could play catch
with you a little longer,
I wouldn't mind
being born again.
So thank you for giving me
this life at least, Father.
I took it all. Every last
thing that mattered to you.
I took your life, your power,
even your precious memories.
Which is why,
I already know that you
don't want to just stand by!
All of you...
[BOTH]
...please help us end this!
[ZEKE]
What a beautiful day it is.
If only I'd had eyes for things
like this sooner, well...
Considering all the
killing I've done,
that'd be too much to ask.
The rumbling just stopped.
What's going on?
[REINER TITAN yells]
Now, Jean! Go!
[JEAN yells]
[PIECK TITAN]
Jean!
[Gasps]
Eren, you damned...
suicidal maniac!
[ANOMALY squeals]
[JEAN] That thing--
it's after Eren's head!
Reiner!
[CONNY]
Jean! Pieck!
We're getting outta here!
Armin's gonna blow
these bones to pieces!
He can't yet!
Reiner's down there!
[PIECK]
I think he'll make it.
The Armored should be
able to withstand
the Colossal's explosion.
And regardless,
to pass up this chance
would be to trample
Reiner's resolve.
[Yells]
[ARMIN]
Thank you.
If you hadn't risen to help us,
then we never could've brought
an end to the rumbling.
[ARMIN]
Goodbye... Eren.
[Inaudible]
[GABI'S DAD] Karina!
You're not hurt, are you?
What in the world just happened?
[ELDIAN H]
That explosion was insane.
[ELDIAN I]
Did everyone make it?
[FALCO'S DAD]
Over there!
Look, the bones.
Does this mean Eren's dead?
[Grunts]
[EREN] As an Ackermann
with awakened powers...
I just couldn't stand
to look at a slave
with no mind of her own...
[MIKASA] That was the
last time we spoke?
Ever since I was a kid,
I've hated you.
[MIKASA]
That can't be.
[Gasps]
[Inaudible]
[CONNY] I won't claim
to have no regrets.
But still, we definitely did
the right thing, didn't we?
I mean, we put an
end to the rumbling.
[ANNIE] They came here from
the internment zone. How?
[KARINA] We were led here by
Mr. Leonhart, your father.
Go and talk to him, dear.
[ANNIE gasps]
I see Armin.
There any sign of Reiner?
--[GABI] Reiner!
--[JEAN] He's okay!
Whoa, what the--?
Look over there!
It's still alive even after
getting hit by that explosion?
Sure is. What the hell
is this thing?
No clue. But I do know that
we can't leave it alive.
[Gasps]
Ah. Well, that figures.
It only makes sense that he
would've survived as well.
Yeah. But what do we do now?
[MIKASA]
Eren.
This is bad!
If that glowing worm thing
finds its way back to Eren,
the rumbling might start again!
[CONNY]
Yeah. We gotta kill it somehow.
If it survived that
explosion point-blank,
we can't kill it.
The one we should
target is Eren.
You all get that, right?
This nightmare won't end
until we take him down.
Sorry, Dad, but I've
got one last job to do.
I'm seeing this
through to the end
'cause it's what Colt would do.
[MIKASA] Why? Why did
it turn out this way?
[Gasps]
[MÜLLER]
Did you hurt your leg?
[ANNIE'S DAD] No, it's been
like this. Thank you.
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER C]
Lift him slowly.
Bring the injured here.
If you hadn't stepped up
and emptied your gun into
the air when you did,
I imagine we'd be at each
other's throats even now.
I've made enough
mistakes in my time.
Let's work together
and overcome this.
[ANNIE'S DAD]
Right.
[ANNIE]
Dad!
A-Annie?
[GABI] Why did that glowing
thing start spewing out gas?
[MIKASA]
Did it die?
No. This isn't the
smell of a dead Titan.
[Gasps]
Could this be the same gas
that they used
on Ragako Village?
[Gasps]
Mikasa! Pieck! Get on Falco!
We need to leave!
I don't get it, what's going on?
'Cause only Ackermanns and Titan
Wielders are immune, remember?
You know what's coming
better than we do,
so you know what needs doing!
But that... that can't be.
It's just too much.
We have to go now!
Wait, we can't! No! Dad! Dad!
[Roars]
[CONNY]
So this is how we go out.
[JEAN]
Guess so.
We'll entrust the rest
to our comrades.
Just like all the Scouts
who came before us did.
[CONNY]
Do you remember, Jean,
the night we had to burn
all those bodies?
[JEAN]
Yeah.
[CONNY]
Well, so you know,
it's your fault that we got
stuck havin' to save humanity.
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER A gasps]
[MIKASA, PIECK gasp]
[REINER]
This is absurd. There's no way.
This isn't happening,
it just can't be!
[ONYANKOPON]
Hey. Hey! Annie!
Are you all right?
What in the world's
going on right now?
[ANNIE gasps]
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER F]
S-Secretary!
[ANOMALY squeals]
[REINER] So... you've
summoned up an army.
Well, I don't give a damn!
I'm still not gonna
let you pass!
You really do enjoy making
life hell, don't you, Eren?
Fine. We'll do things your way.
I'll see this
through to the end!
[REINER TITAN roaring]
[REINER]
Conny. Jean. Gabi!
No. Is that... Mom?
[Roars]
[REINER]
Pieck! Annie!
[ANNIE screams]
[REINER] Damn it.
When will this torture end?
[Yells]
[LEVI]
Mikasa? Pull it together!
There's nobody else
who can kill Eren.
It has to be us!
[MIKASA]
It's too much.
I can't take it anymore.
[Inaudible]
[MIKASA]
I wanna go back.
I just want to go back home.
[EREN]
Mikasa. Wake up.
You'll catch a cold.
Eren?
Wait, I'm confused.
When did I fall asleep?
[Thud]
Not sure, but you
must've been exhausted.
[MIKASA] I feel like I just
woke from a really long dream.
Well, it's nothing
to worry about now.
We can take it easy today.
I caught some pretty
big fish, so--
Uh. Mikasa?
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
But I feel like this isn't
where I should be right now.
There's nothing
we can do anymore.
[MIKASA]
Huh?
[EREN] On the day we ran
away and came here,
we gave up our chance
to change things.
Marley's war ended
two months ago,
so the invasion of Paradis
should start pretty soon,
and running is the
only way to survive.
It's hard though.
I'm sure that Armin's been
desperate to find us.
But there's no way
I could make Historia
become part of that
hellish cycle of killing,
and I can't commit genocide
against everyone
past the walls either.
So let's leave
and live out the four years
I've got left in peace.
We'll find somewhere quiet.
Just you and me.
That's what you said,
Mikasa. You wanted this.
[MIKASA]
Yeah.
Sorry.
I know we promised not
to talk about that stuff.
Do you mind making
another promise?
Once I'm dead and gone,
please throw this scarf away.
You're gonna live without
me for a long time.
So forget you knew me.
Forget, and be free.
[EREN]
Please, Mikasa. Forget about me.
[MIKASA]
I'm sorry.
I can't.
[MIKASA]
Eren's inside the mouth!
Everyone! Help me reach him!
[LEVI]
Understood, Mikasa!
Eren!
[Yells]
I'll see you later, Eren.
I understand that you
only did it for the sake
of the future you saw with
the Attack Titan's ability,
but I'm having trouble believing
that you had to beat me
till I was spitting blood.
Like, was that knee
to the gut necessary?
I was doing everything I
could to push you two away.
It seemed kinda crazy to me,
too, even as I was doing it.
But I just let the
moment take over.
I'm really sorry.
[ARMIN] Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to Mikasa.
She's the one you hurt
with your bullshit.
Ugh. Yeah, you're right.
So you did all that
to push us away, huh?
To make us turn against you
and become the heroes
who prevent the annihilation of
the human race by killing you.
You got it.
Every human left in the
world outside the walls
will owe you a debt
of gratitude.
You'll be known as
the Island Devils
who stood against
your own homeland
in order to save humanity.
I'm pretty sure it'll make you
the most respected
people in the world.
So you're hoping we can all
become like the Tybur family.
You hope we'll have
enough influence
to protect Paradis
from reprisal.
Well, we're not heroes,
and we won't pretend to be.
Sorry, Eren, hate to disappoint,
but after what you pulled,
don't assume we'll
"hop to" for you.
[ARMIN]
Where you going?
To the places we always
dreamed about seeing.
As we walk, I'll tell you more
about what happened with Ymir.
[BOTH gasp]
[EREN] So this is fire
that flows like water.
[ARMIN] It really is.
It's even formed into rivers.
Anyway, where did I leave off?
You were saying the Founder Ymir
has continued to obey King
Fritz for 2,000 years.
You said that's why the Power
of the Titans still exists.
Right.
He burned her home down,
killed her parents,
and ripped out her
tongue, to boot.
And yet, even after
attaining godlike power,
she went on serving him.
[ARMIN]
Why?
What could've compelled
her to do that?
When I touched her in the
Paths, I felt the answer.
Hard to believe as it may seem.
The Founder Ymir...
she loved King Fritz.
[ARMIN gasps]
There it is.
That's what kept her bound to
him as 2,000 years went past.
[EREN] I'm a long way
from understanding
what's in the depths
of Ymir's heart.
But she'd clearly
been suffering
through every one
of those years.
She spent them seeking the
person who would release her.
Then, that person appeared.
And it was Mikasa.
[ARMIN]
Huh? Did you say "Mikasa"?
[EREN]
Sure did.
You're not drifting
off, are you?
[ARMIN]
Of course I'm not!
But tell me, why Mikasa?
Not sure.
To find out, you'd have
to ask Ymir herself.
Honestly, not even I know
what Mikasa will do.
The only thing I know for a fact
is the outcome of
Mikasa's choice.
It's what I keep moving
forward to reach.
I slaughter most of humanity
and trigger a civil
war in Paradis.
What's more, I give my
best friends no choice
except to face me and
the Founder in battle.
I've got no clue if they live.
So that's the future you
saw at the medal ceremony.
Yeah, but...
Ever since I obtained the
power of the Founding Titan,
my head has become
a complete mess.
The past and future--
it's all happening at once.
And so, I had no choice.
That day, in that moment,
Bertholdt would've died,
but he had to live.
[Gasps]
[EREN]
So I...
So I sent it away from
him and towards Mom.
Let's go, Eren.
Okay.
All right, so how did
things go with her?
With her?
I mean with Mikasa.
Do you really think she's
gonna be able to forget you
and live happily with
somebody else?
That's what you're hoping
she'll do, right?
Uh, I don't know.
[EREN]
Ow.
The hell kind of answer is that?
Listen, I still
haven't forgiven you!
Just who do you think you are
to disregard Mikasa's
feelings like that?!
She always valued you over
everything, even her own life!
You really think you could
just say, "Forget about me,"
and that'd be the end of it?
You're a selfish heartbreaker.
And I hope she does
forget about you
because she deserves
to be happy.
But, hey, the good news is,
I know of one
charming young fella
she's pretty close to already!
[EREN]
No. That'd break my heart.
I don't want her to
find someone else!
I wanna be her one
and only love!
Even if she does get over me,
I think it should take
her ten years at least!
[ARMIN]
Oh. I see.
Sorry, I-I didn't think you'd
say something that pathetic.
[EREN]
Don't tell Mikasa about this.
I want her to find
happiness. I do.
But I...
[EREN]
Damn it.
I don't wanna die.
I just want to stay with
Mikasa. With all of you.
[ARMIN]
Eren! We don't have to give up.
We can find another way!
We can't!
I'm sure all the people I
crushed wanted to live, too.
And yet... I--
[EREN]
Eighty percent.
Huh?
I end up killing
80% of humanity.
No. How could you?!
Why? Eren!
I know that I try to eradicate
all of humanity
outside the walls.
And by the time I'm killed...
...four in five people are
dead and the greater world
is reduced to the
level of civilization
that we have in Paradis.
Meaning, there won't be a
one-sided war of reprisal
like you feared.
Though this conflict
doesn't end.
[ARMIN]
What the hell do you mean?
Are you telling me that
all of this is pointless?
The massacre hasn't even
happened yet! Just stop it!
[EREN]
I can't.
Twenty percent of humanity is as
much as you can manage to save.
It's been determined.
"Been determined"?
But you determined it!
You're the one who kills them!
I can't tell you how many
times I tried and failed
to change what comes to pass.
But things always turn
out exactly as I saw
in all my memories
of the future.
You were right.
I'm not free, Armin.
I'm a slave to freedom.
No. None of this makes
any damn sense!
So... it hasn't happened,
but it can't be undone?
Do you know how completely
deranged this is?
It isn't a solution,
it's another nightmare!
What, you can't have
war if everyone's dead?
How could someone see that
as more than a bad joke?
Eren, there may be no end
in sight for this conflict,
and I'm sure history
is full of people
going through the same hell
we did, over and over.
But we still need to believe
that on some distant day
we can all understand
each other.
And now, that fragile
hope is just... gone.
You trampled it, Eren.
The only lesson left
is "kill or be killed."
That's it.
And you're trying to say
that you did this for us?
[GRISHA] Eren. That's the
name we picked for you.
No, that's... that's not true.
Yeah.
And, Eren, you're free.
I flattened the world
because I wanted to.
Because I wanted
to see this sight.
[ARMIN]
Why?
I don't actually know why.
I just know that I
wanted it so very badly.
Of course, I told myself
that I was doing it
to protect all of you.
But Sasha and Hange both died
'cause of my actions.
And I'm the one who put
all of you and Floch
at each others throats.
Why? Why did it
turn out this way?
I finally know.
Because I'm an idiot.
I'm nothing more than
a garden-variety idiot
who got his hands on power.
That's why this is the only
resolution I can bring about.
Heh. That's all there is to it.
[ARMIN]
I get it.
I get why you wanted
to erase humanity
from the world beyond the walls.
I've felt the same.
You liar. You would never
stoop to something so--
[ARMIN]
Nobody will ever guess it
since I'm a hero who saved
20% of all people.
But still, it was me
who showed you the book
that formed the basis
for your worldview.
That dumb idea--
of a free, unoccupied world
waiting to be conquered--
was mine.
What is that?
I'm glad that you finally
noticed it, Eren.
It's been right here at
our feet this whole time,
but you were always looking
off into the distance.
Thank you, Eren.
For showing me what
was beyond the walls.
And for showing me this sight.
Both of us are responsible
for what happened.
So, yeah, I figure in the end,
I'll, well, be joining you.
You're joining me? Where?
Assuming it exists, in hell.
We'll spend eternity suffering
for every single
life that we stole.
Together.
I have to let you go now.
I'm erasing your memory
of our time here.
But when our next meeting ends,
it'll all come back to you.
Yeah, 'cause it'll
end with you dead.
And when we meet
again after that...
[EREN] Yeah. Look for me
in hell. I'll be waiting.
[ARMIN] Right. We'll be
together, for all time.
[ANNIE]
So your wounds are all better?
[ARMIN]
Annie?
[ARMIN] Yeah, they've had
enough time to heal.
It's all come back
to me. All of it.
[MIKASA]
Armin.
[ARMIN wails]
You got your memories
back, too, right?
Of the times Eren
reached out to talk to us?
I did.
He said that... that you
would make a choice,
and that in the end,
it would cause the
Power of the Titans
to be erased from this world.
He talked to me, too.
What a conscientious
piece of shit.
Eren... I can't believe you.
Listen to this.
Eren told me that my mom
would turn back into a human.
He told me that he hoped
we would all live long lives.
But what about you?
Why didn't you worry about
yourself? You suicidal maniac.
Wow. I'm feeling kinda left out.
Wish I'd gotten a chat.
Welcome home, Annie.
[ANNIE]
It's good to be back, Dad.
Gabi!
Well, look who showed up.
Were you watching?
It would seem that this is it.
This is what we did with
the hearts you gave.
[CONNY]
Sasha.
--[GABI] Mom! Dad!
--[GABI'S DAD] My sweet girl.
[FALCO]
Gabi! Hey!
[Gasps] Falco!
[REINER]
Mom, I, uh...
I don't think that I'm
the Armored Titan anymore.
[KARINA] Really?
That's wonderful, Riener.
I'm so sorry for
everything. All of it.
I finally see that you were
the only thing I ever needed.
[MIKASA]
I should go now.
Huh? Why?
Because if I were to stay
here, they'd take Eren.
And there's no way they'd
give him a good burial.
[ARMIN]
Good point.
We should let him rest
somewhere nice and quiet.
[MIKASA] Maybe the place where
we always found him napping.
I think that's a good spot.
[ANNIE'S DAD] Please,
Secretary Müller, listen.
Eren Jaeger is dead and gone,
and the Power of the Titans
was destroyed with him!
We're just people now.
Nothing more!
Can you prove that for
a fact? Here, and now?
If you took a blood
test, we could--
[MÜLLER]
I said here and now!
So please, find a way
to convince me...
...that you are humans,
not monsters.
If we still had the ability
to transform into Titans,
we'd be using it
to defend ourselves.
But, no.
Even as we stare down
the barrels of your guns,
we remain powerless.
There can be no greater
proof that we're human.
Who are you?
I'm an Eldian from Paradis.
My name is Armin Arlelt.
And I killed Eren Jaeger.
I stopped the Attack Titan,
and ended the rumbling.
It was you, wasn't it?
All this time, it was you...
peeking into my head.
Your life was stolen,
and your love was a nightmare.
None of the lives lost can
ever be brought back, but...
...it's because of the lives
you created that I'm here.
[MIKASA]
So rest in peace, Ymir.
[CHRISTA]
Three years after the so-called
"Battle of Heaven and Earth,"
there are still far more people
dead than left to mourn.
As for those who did survive,
they surely still suffer
from unhealed wounds.
[CHRISTA] As those battered
people try to rebuild,
their worst fears
are coming true.
Under Jaegerist rule,
the nation of Eldia
is rapidly building
its military strength.
Out of fear of reprisal from
the survivors of humanity
across the sea, the island
shouts with one voice:
"Kill or be killed.
Fight for your life.
The only way to
live is to fight.
So fight. Fight."
The end of Titans does not mean
the end to this conflict.
Eren made that clear
when he gave me his
knowledge of the future.
The future Eren showed
me is behind us now,
but his knowledge has left me
with a clear perspective
on these events.
I'm certain that this outcome
was not the result
of Eren's choices alone.
All of us add shape
and color to the world
with every choice we make.
Perhaps this
generation is cursed
to live lives
divorced from peace.
But if we must fight, let it
be for an end to fighting.
Eren feared that
this war would go on
until either Eldia
or the world was gone.
But in the end,
he left it in our hands.
Now, with this brief reprieve,
comes our chance to choose...
..."how to live in a world
without Titans."
Even Historia's
handwriting is beautiful.
I can't get over it.
Smells good, too.
[JEAN]
As I've said before,
you really shouldn't lust
after married women.
It's creepy.
I can't help but notice
that you're becoming
increasingly fixated
on your hair.
Just who are you
trying to impress?
The ladies who'll see my picture
when they're reading
history books.
They're gonna think
they're reading
the Field Guide to Horses.
[JEAN] You know, it's a real shame
your life got longer, Reiner.
Tch.
Paradis Island's in view now.
Hey, Armin. Do you seriously
think that this'll work?
We destroyed the walls.
You betrayed the island.
And we all helped kill Eren,
who these people revere.
Yet the Allied Forces sent us
to handle these peace talks?
Ambassadors or not,
I wouldn't be surprised
if we got blown out of
the water pretty soon.
Yeah. I'm amazed it
hasn't happened already.
Well, this is what we get
for letting that dumbass
make us "international heroes."
Hah. So much for
"living long lives."
Come on, Annie.
Don't tell me you
got on this ship
expecting to go home alive.
No, but we're all hoping
that there's a chance.
I mean, none of us came here
to commit suicide, right?
Walking back into what might be
hell is the right thing to do.
And don't forget that
we're Scout Regiment.
We're a bunch of dreamers
who don't know when to quit.
But I was in the
Military Police.
Anyway, we won't
be killed at once.
'Cause when the people
of Paradis see us,
they'll want to know...
...what we have to say.
[ARMIN] After trying to kill
each other again and again,
we put down our weapons
and began to call for peace.
[ARMIN] They'll ask us, "Why?"
What did we see?
[ARMIN] And we'll tell
them the whole story.
[MIKASA] Eren, the others
are coming to visit soon.
Won't that be nice?
♪ Closing Song ♪
[Gasps]
[Sobbing]
I... I just want
to see you again.
[Gasps]
[MIKASA] Thank you for wrapping
this scarf around me, Eren.
www.tvsubtitles.net